http://www.ukmgparts.com/privacy-policy-1

ZS
Rover 75 & ZT V8 (260)
ZS
Rover 75 & ZT V8 (260)
GENERAL
This privacy statement sets out how BROWN AND GAMMONS Limited comply with European Union data protection requirements. This applies to the entire web site. BROWN AND GAMMONS LTD are committed to respecting your privacy. We have structured our web site so that, in general, you can visit BROWN AND GAMMONS LTD on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide us with any information by which you can be identified, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. For your protection, we are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and have given all appropriate notifications to the Information Commissioner.
WHAT WE COLLECT
Prior to supplying parts orders, we will collect the following information:
Name & addresses
Telephone number
Email address
Anyone signing up for news or information from BROWN AND GAMMONS LTD may choose to unsubscribe in each edition released.
We may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with our products, and contact preferences in order to provide you with further correspondence about our products and services.
When you visit our site, we may also log your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access device.
Some pages use cookies, a data analysis technique. In order to learn more about the use of cookies, please see below.
WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER?
We will use this information and data obtained from other sources in order to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following purposes:
Internal record keeping and administration;
Marketing;
To improve our products and services;
To ensure that the content, services and advertising that we offer is tailored to your needs and interests we may keep your information for a reasonable period for these purposes.
WHO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WITH AND YOUR CHOICES
When you use this site and have not advised us to the contrary, you are agreeing that we may use your personal information for the purposes set out in this statement and in order to do this, we may need to share your information with our service providers and agents. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties (other than our subsidiaries, parent companies and business partners in the automotive and manufacturing sectors) unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may release your personal information to our authorized direct marketing agents unless you tell us that you do not wish this to happen.
When you provide any information online, you should look for the box which you can click to say that you do not want the information to be used by anyone for direct marketing purposes. If you have not previously objected to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us at:
Data Protection Compliance Officer
Brown & Gammons Ltd
18 High Street
Baldock
Herts
SG7 6AS
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write or e-mail us as soon as possible to the above address.
By providing us with your personal information, you consent to our processing any sensitive personal data, for the purposes mentioned above. You also consent to our transferring your information to countries or jurisdictions which do not provide the same level of data protection as the UK, if necessary for the above purposes. If we do make such a transfer, we will, if appropriate, put a contract in place to ensure that your information is protected.
SECURITY
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on line.
OTHER WEBSITES
Our web site may contain links to enable you to visit other web sites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site you should note that we do not have any control over that other web site. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and this privacy statement does not govern such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the web site in question.
HOW WE USE COOKIES
A cookie is a piece of text that asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, your browser adds that text in a small file. A cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. For example, when you visit an electronic store, a cookie makes it easier to shop, by allowing you to place things into a shopping basket; the basket itself is not the cookie, the cookie is placed on your hard drive and keeps track of your basket versus others in use at the same time.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our web site in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Denial of a traffic log cookie should not prevent you from using one of these sites.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better web site, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. This practice is strictly in force. We know that people have concerns about cookies, but we believe that the benefit we both gain from their proper use is worthwhile. You may set your web browser (Microsoft internet explorer or Netscape navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests or decline cookies completely. You can delete the files that contain cookies - those files are stored as part of your internet browser.
This data protection notice may change and therefore you should review it regularly. We will of course notify you of any changes where we are required to do so.
Basket
You have 0 Items - £0.00
View Basket
Quick Search
Search products by choosing a category and entering a name or code.
Rover 75 & ZT V8 (260)
